[Music]
glitter in the
you need a little bit of company you met
me at the perfect time
i want you baby
[Music]
i need you
come on dance with me
[Music]
i'm one of the greatest ain't no debate
no no i'm still levitated i'm heavily
medicated ironic i gave him love and
they end up hating on me she told me she
love me and she been waiting fighting
hard for your love and i'm running thin
on my patients needing someone to hug
even took it back to the base you see
what you got me out here doing mighty
threw me off but can't nobody start the
movement
let's go left foot right foot levitate
pop stars do a leaping with the baby i
had to lace my shoes for the blessings i
was chasing if i ever slip i fall into a
better situation so catch up go put some
cheese on it get out and get your bread
up they always leaving you father but
you run together weight of the world on
my shoulders i kept my head up now baby
stand up cause girl you want me i want
you baby
[Music]
i need
you all night come on
[Music]
to i can't stop yeah
[Applause]
[Music]
i need you
all night come on
[Music]
me
come on destiny
[Music]
[Applause]
you